Never Take Off the Mask
The Lone Ranger is a action, adventure, western film directed by Gore Verbinski.
The Texas Rangers chase down a gang of outlaws led by Butch Cavendish, but
the gang ambushes the Rangers, seemingly killing them all.
One survivor is found, however, by an American Indian
named Tonto, who nurses him back to health.
The Ranger, donning a mask and riding a white stallion named Silver, teams up with
Tonto to bring the unscrupulous gang and others of that ilk to justice.
Tonto, played by Johnny Depp.
John Reid / The Lone Ranger, played by Armie Hammer.
Cole, played by Tom Wilkinson.
Butch Cavendish, played by William Fichtner.
Red Harrington, played by Helena Bonham Carter.
Fuller, played by Barry Pepper.
The Lone Ranger is a 2013 American Western action film directed by Gore
Verbinski and written by Justin Haythe, Ted Elliott and Terry Rossio.
Based on the title character of the same name, the film stars Johnny Depp as Tonto, the
narrator of the events, and Armie Hammer as John Reid, the Lone Ranger.
The story tells through Tonto's memories of the duo's earliest efforts to
subdue local villainy and bring justice to the American Old West.
William Fichtner, Barry Pepper, Ruth Wilson, James Badge Dale, Tom Wilkinson
and Helena Bonham Carter are featured in supporting roles.
This was the first theatrical film featuring the Lone
Ranger and Tonto characters since William A.
Fraker's 1981 film, The Legend of the Lone Ranger.
Produced by Walt Disney Pictures, Jerry Bruckheimer Films, Blind Wink Productions, and Infinitum Nihil, production was
plagued with problems and budgetary concerns, which at one point almost led to the film's premature cancellation.
The film premiered at the Hyperion Theater at Disney California Adventure Park on June 22,
2013, and was released theatrically in the United States on July 3, 2013.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics and grossed only $260.5 million worldwide against an estimated $225–250 million production budget and
an additional $150 million in marketing costs, making it one of the biggest box-office bombs of all time, losing Disney over $160–190 million.
It was nominated at the 86th Academy Awards in two categories for
Best Visual Effects and Best Makeup and Hairstyling.
The film explores themes of escape, texas, texas ranger, horse, native american.